hey today we're going to do a quick
tutorial on how to do gel overlay with
the no file method we're going to start
with a slip layer of gel also called a
wedding layer don't cure it get as close
as you can to
the cuticle area without touching the
skin don't touch the damn skin and then
you're going to take a dollop you're
going to swirl it up towards the top of
the nail and you're going to start
swooping down don't touch the cuticle
area swoop swoop grab more gel if you
need
make sure you keep that gel towards the
middle of the nail that's where you want
your apex to sit and swoop swoop swoop
soup swoop then drag downwards towards
the end of the nail because you don't
want too much gel to sit there then what
you're going to do is flip the finger
over
so that the gel can
pool towards the middle of the nail drag
any lumps and bumps down towards the
middle so you get that nice apex oh yeah
look at that
bam